BENJAMIN SOLT

FULL STACK ENGINEER

SUMMARY

Customer service professional with 10 years of experience resolving complex customer inquiries.

Passionate about building strong customer relationships and promoting company image.

Past experience in coding, freelance art, and 3D art/animation.

Took initiative to self teach Epic Game's Unreal Engine.

SKILLS

- WordPress
- CSS
- HTML
- JavaScript
- Javascript
- React
- Helpful
- Friendly
- Empathic

- Firebase
- Patient
- Dependable
- Communication Skills
- Customer Service
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Adobe Creative 3d
- Unreal Engine
- 3D Studio Max

EDUCATION

BLOOMTECH - REMOTE (WAS CALLED LAMBDA)

July 2019 - August 2020 Full Stack Engineer

- HTLM, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux
- Jest, Python, GitHub, Node.js

TEMPLE UNIVERSITY - AMBLER, PA CERTIFICATION IN WEBSITE DESIGN

May 2012

- Intensive course focused on creative web design
- Page layouts and art assets
- Utilized HTML, CSS, and Dreamweaver

THE ART INSTITUTE OF PHILADELPHIA

December 2007

• Bachelor of Science Degree in Media Arts and Animation

CONTACT INFO

- Bensolt@gmail.com
- Cell: 215 360 5410
- Fort Washington, PA
- Bensolt.com
- Github
- linkedIn

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

INERTIA MARKETING - DIGITAL PRODUCTION

MAY 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

- Created websites/landing pages for clients using WordPress
- Created HTML monthly emails
- Created a guess game with JavaScript, HTML, CSS

METRO ESPORTS - STEM INSTRUCTOR

OCTOBER 2021 - JUNE 2022

- Taught introductory programming classes with JavaScript in person and remote
- Answer inquiries and helped students solve coding errors.

GROA - FRONT END DEVELOPER

FEBRUARY - APRIL 2020

Built to recommend movies to user, based on how user rates movies HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React | AWS

- As Front End Developer built Authorization, Login, display layout of movie info
- Solved problems and trouble shot bugs with team members
- Collaborated remotely with team of 6 web developers, 2 data science, and 1 UX designer

LOGO AND ART ASSET DESIGNER

WILLOW GROVE, PA NOVEMBER 2013 – NOVEMBER 2014

- Created logos and t-shirt graphics, to meet companies needs
- Animated, modeled and textured 3D art assets to visually show and document how the system works
- Created 3D rotation of a medical device to share with internal and external stakeholders

PROJECTS PORTFOLIO

APRIL 2020 - 2022

Built to showcase personal projects HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React

 Designed, developed and implemented React based site to display a diverse range of personal projects

REACT-REDUX-APP2

DECEMBER 2019

Built to demonstrate API call and Redux HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React | Halo API

- Implemented Halo API database to visualize data from site
- Built a filter to allow a user to search by name of player